Fall in love with the grumpiest man in America.
A Man Called Otto is a comedy, drama film directed by Marc Forster.
When a lively young family moves in next door, grumpy widower Otto Anderson meets his match in a quick-witted,
pregnant woman named Marisol, leading to an unlikely friendship that turns his world upside down.
Otto Anderson, played by Tom Hanks.
Marisol, played by Mariana Treviño.
Jimmy, played by Cameron Britton.
Malcolm, played by Mack Bayda.
Tommy, played by Manuel Garcia-Rulfo.
Anita, played by Juanita Jennings.
A Man Called Otto is a 2022 American comedy-drama film directed
by Marc Forster from a screenplay by David Magee.
It is a remake of the 2015 Swedish film A Man Called Ove, which was based
on the 2012 novel of the same name by Fredrik Backman.
The film stars Tom Hanks and his son Truman in the title role, with Mariana
Treviño, Rachel Keller, and Manuel Garcia-Rulfo in supporting roles.
The plot follows a bitter old man who reluctantly gets
involved in the lives of his neighbors.
A Man Called Otto began a limited theatrical release on December 29, 2022, before a wide
release in the United States on January 13, 2023, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $113
million worldwide against a $50 million production budget.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel or
book, suicide attempt, melancholy, flashback.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.